armorama.com 2003-04-12

# Military Scale Model Community - Armorama.com - Model and Diorama Features, Forums, Gallery, and More.

|    
|  |   
---  

What is Your Privacy Statement?Category: Main >> What is Your Privacy Statement?   
| Answer  
---  
 **·**   What about my privacy?

Your personal information will never be sold or given to any third party. We may from time to time, email you with special announcments concerning site events or upgrades. These will not be in the form of marketing emails (as in trying to sell you something).

Top  

* * *

 **·**   What else do you know about me?

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

Top  

* * *

 **·**   Does this site use cookies?

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at the site. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

Top  

* * *

 **·**   Can I cancel my registration?

Yes. At any time you may discontinue your registration here at Armorama.com. If requested we will purge all your personal data from the database. We hope you never ask though. :)

Top  

* * *

Copyright ©2003 Armorama.com and [Wandering Knights LLC](http://wanderingknights.com/). All Rights Reserved. Read our privacy statement. Advertise on Armorama.
